There was no way for Moses,
if the Red Sea was not divided
Are you with me?
There was no way for Moses, if the Red sea was not divided.
Moses was at the cross roads
He looked here; he looked there,there was no way.
the only way was just to cross the Red sea.
In the same way, many of you are in the crossroads
There is no way
In any area of your life,that you find difficulty to penetrate
I want you to raise your prayer mantle; prayer sword and begin to part and divide
And make way where there is no way
Are you ready with me?
YES!
I cant hear you?
You know your prayer has a sword
when you raise the voice, confession of The Holy Spirit it is a sword, a weapon
That can divide and make a way where there is no way
You just need this Word.
And I am going to anoint your word; every word you are going to speak am going to anoint it.
Every word you are going to speak at this moment; be anointed in the name of Jesus
Every word that will come out of your voice, your utterance - be anointed in the name of Jesus!
AMEN!
When your word is anointed, you can divide and make a way where there is no way in your business.
And make a way where there is no way in your career.
AMEN!
And make a way where there is no way in your finances!
And make a way where there is no way in your health.
AMEN!
And make a way where there is no way in your career,
Make a way where there is no way in your marriage,
AMEN!
Open your lips and begin to talk right now
In the Mighty name of Jesus Christ!
AMEN!
I anoint your word!
The word that will come out of you, be anointed!
AMEN!
From now let the Word that will come out of you be anointed!
Because you don't believe in yourself and you don't believe you can part- you can divide
You don't believe you can walk with your word
You don't believe you can open with your word
I anoint your word - be anointed!
BE ANOINTED!
Get out!
Open your lips and be filled by the Holy Ghost!
HOLY GHOST!
Thank you Lord!
Open your lips and begin to talk, talk! talk! talk!
In the Mighty name of Jesus!
Amen!
Listen, listen to the voice of God!
Your voice has been anointed!
Amen!
I command every difficulty to surmounted
AMEN!
Your challenges- be surmounted!
Your situation - be surmounted!
Begin to match out of your challenges!
Match out of your situations!
In the mighty Name of Jesus!
She has something to vomit,because she is a spiritualist.
She is a seer - she inherited it
It is a family processing, she is being given that power.
Its power - but negative, she has something to say
Hallelujah!
wave your hand.
Listen to me, there was no way for Moses if the Red Sea was not divided.
There was no way for Moses if the Red Sea was not divided!
Any area of your life , that you find difficult to penetrate - Right now begin to penetrate.
Make a way where there is no way !
Be it your business - make a way where there is no way
Be it your finances - make a way where there is no way.
Be it your marriage, - Make a way where there is no way.
Be it your health, - Make a way where there is no way.
Be it your career, - Make a way where there is no way.
Begin to make a way -
Open your lips and begin to part
Viewers all over the world, where can we go from his presence?
There was no way for Moses, If the Red Sea was not parted.
There was no way for Moses, If the Red Sea was not divided.
Any area in your life that you find difficulty to penetrate, be it your business, be it your career,
be it your finances, be it your marriage, be it your health - begin to penetrate right now.
breakthrough
Make a way where there is no way
In the name of Jesus!
In the Mighty name of Jesus!
I deliver you from any satanic covenant-
Covenant of attitude, covenant of character - Be delivered!
AMEN!
BE DELIVERED!
Begin to deliver yourself, release yourself
Open your lips and begin to release yourself from any satanic covenant
Covenant of attitude, covenant of character, any satanic covenant
Covenant of attitude, covenant of character, covenant of behavior
begin to release your self, release your self.
Get your self out of this covenant
You are released!
be released!
Viewers all over the world, right now I release you from any satanic covenant-
Any satanic covenant
Covenant of attitude, covenant of behaviour, Covenant of attitude, covenant of character.
BE RELEASED!
In Jesus name!
{I want to kill her, Because she has a great ministry- she is going to win a lot of souls for christ!}
In Jesus Christ Name we pray!
Yes, I want to pray for you,
I say to you, be released from any covenant!
Be released from any satanic covenant!
Covenant of attitude!
Be released - from covenant of attitude!
Be released - from covenant of character!
Be released - from covenant of behavior!
Be released!
I release you in the name of Jesus!
Speak to yourself!
You can know if you are released!
Thank you Lord!
Give thanks to God!
The Lord is good -all the time! All the time- the Lord is good!
Give thanks to Him!
That is passion for man, the relationship with man
In the Name of Jesus Christ!
Worship Him!
(because he lives, I can face tomorrow)
(Because he lives all fear is gone)
He is Living in you now
You can face tomorrow- he is living in you!
Confess it now!
Say. He is living in me!
Confess it, Confess it, Confess it!
He is living in me!
I can face tomorrow!
I can face next time!
I can face next challenge!
I can face next moment!
Now, he is living in me!
(Because he live I can face tomorrow!)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know He holds my future!)
(My live is worth a living just because He lives!)
(Because he lives I can face tomorrow)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know He holds my future!)
(My live is worth a living just because He lives!)
(Because he lives I can face tomorrow)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know He holds my future!)
(My live is worth a living just because He lives!)
hallelujah!
You may not know the reason why I sing this song!
The Lord said to me, "Joshua, I am living in the temple of your people".
And I asked, "Who are my people?"
Those whom Jesus sent me to.
He says he is living in you,
now that he is living in you, you can face tomorrow!
He is living in you, you can face your challenges!
He is living in you, you can face your situation!
He is living in you, you can face the next moment!
He is living in me, I can face the next moment!
Say he is living in me, I can face the next!
(Because he live I can face tomorrow!)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know, he hold my future!)
(My life is worth living just, because he lives!)
(Because he live I can face tomorrow!)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know, he holds my future!)
(My life is worth living just, because he lives!)
Instead of tomorrow, it is a bit too far- I can face next!
(Because he lives, I can face next-)
(Because he lives, all fear is gone)
(Because I know, he holds my future!)
(My life is worth living just, because he lives!)
Right now, there is an ability in you! there is enablement to face next!
To face next!
Next is when you leave here immediately
After the grace, It is next.
After the grace, there is an ability to face next!
There is capability- you have the capacity to face next!
When they come against you twice, you come against them hundred times!
Speak to yourself, there is enablement. there is ability from God to face next.
Speak out, Speak out!
Confess it, confess it!
Begin to confess that ability, that enablement to face next!
to face next!
In Jesus name!
You know you are not alone!
I said, "you are not alone!"
Those who are for you, supporting you are more than those who are against you!
That is the ability to face next!
Because those who are for you, those who are with you, who are supporting you!
Those who believe in you, those who speak to you, those who speak for you!
Are more than, those who are against you!
Confess it, I am not alone. Now, I can face next!
Because those who are for me, with me, supporting me
are more than those who are against me
Confess! confess! confess! confess!
Begin them, confess them!
In Jesus christ name we pray !
Now, there is so much anointing, let us put our demand on it
Come on, Confess, confess, confess!
put your demand on it!
Begin to put your demand, anointing is everywhere!
Power, grace, put your demand
We must put a demand on this anointing!
Right now by confessing.
I am not alone; I can face next because those who are with me, supporting me,
Those who are with me, fighting for me, are more than those who are against me
Confess, Confess, Confess!
Viewers all over the world, you are not alone.
Viewer are you sick? Are you on the sick bed?
What is your challenge? what is your situation?
You are not alone!
There is ability, there is strength from God for you.
Because, those who are with, supporting you , fighting for you, praying for you
with you, are more than those who are against you
You are not alone, confess it viewers begin to confess it.
"I am not alone" confess it - so shall it be!
Begin to confess them, I am not alone, I am not alone, I sense it, I believe it!
I am not alone!
If they come against you with their sickness, if they come against you with their disease
with their infirmity, you are not alone, confess it! In the name of Jesus!
Wave your hands and say thank you Lord!
I can see the finger of God in your life!
Amen!
I can see the ability of God in your life!
I can see the enablement!
Amen!
I can see the enablement
I can see those who are fighting for you,
Amen!
I can see those who are supporting you,
I can see those who are praying for you!
Amen!
I can see those who believe in you!
They are more than those who are against you,
Amen!
I say, they are more than those who are against you
Amen
Worship him, worship him!
Give thanks to him, with all your heart
With all my heart, I say" thank you!"
With all my heart I say, "thank you!"
Because those who are with me, those who are supporting me,
those who are praying for me, those who are with me.
Are more, more, more than those who are against me.
In Jesus Christ name!
Amen!
What will I say?
I can see breakthrough!
Amen!
Breakthrough!
Viewers all over the world I know you know what we are going through
Because you are going through the same atmosphere, I say, be blessed!
in the name of Jesus!
The voice of God says, Breakthrough!
Amen!
Breakthrough!
I feel that breakthrough here
Viewers at home, I know you are feeling it the same!
If you are feeling that breakthrough begin to confess your breakthrough!
Begin to confess that breakthrough!
Because you are released from their disease!
You are released from their hardship !
You are released from iniquities !
You are given grace- Mighty Grace- Confess it!
Confess it, confess it!
Rejoice!
You are enabled for the next because I can see viewer - those who are with you ,
Supporting you, those who are with you, praying for you,
Those who are with you are more than those who are against you!
Right now can you wave the flag of your nation- stand for your nation, country!
Every area of challenge, every loopholes- pray for your nation.
Begin to pray for your nation
Pray for your nation- pray for your country.
Deliver your nation- begin to deliver your nation!
Realise your country from every spirit, every covenant, every satanic covenant
Every satanic covenant, every satanic covenant!
Begin to realise your nation , from corruption,misuse and misappropriation
Realise your nation from killing stealing and distructions
Release your nation from disunity
Begin to realise your nation!
In the mighty Name of Jesus!
I want to hear your crying for your nation
Say, Lord Jesus, redeem my leader, my nation.
Begin to redeem your nation, your leader, redeem them.
God's intervention!
In the mighty Name of Jesus christ!
Glory be to God Almighty !
Right now you can begin to confess whom you are!
Are you here to rededicate yourself or you are rededicated already?
Or you are coming to christ for the first time
Hallelujah!
Open your lips and begin to confess whom you are and walk in the light of whom you are.
Lord Jesus, Come into my heart and wash me with your precious blood.
Wash me with Your precious blood
Open your lips and begin to wash your soul, your spirit with His precious blood.
Nothing like it - so special, so dear
begin to wash your soul, your spirit with His precious blood
Ask him to make you an agent of light where there is darkness.
Make me an agent of obedience where there is disobedience!
Make me an agent of humility where there is pride
Make me an channel of pardon where there is injury.
Make me a channel of righteousness where there is sin.
~Open your lips~
In the mighty name of Jesus
Open your lips once again and ask him to make me an channel of pardon where there is injury.
A channel of righteousness where there is iniquity, where there is sin.
Ask him to make you a channel of obedience where there is disobedience!
A channel of faithfulness where there is unfaithfulness!
Make me a channel of Shining light where there is darkness.
In Jesus Christ name we pray!
AMEN!
Tell your neighbour ~ you need to know how much you need Jesus!
Again and Again!
In order to maintain your blessing
In order to maintain your miracle - you need to know how much you need Jesus!
I need Jesus to bath
I need Jesus to laugh
I need Jesus to dress
I need Jesus to greet
I need Jesus to sit
I need Jesus to stand
I need Jesus to frown
I need Jesus to smile
I need Jesus!
Just have that message- that you need Jesus to frown
God says, there is time for everything, time to smile, time to frown!
You need Jesus to frown
You need Jesus to smile
You need Jesus to sit
You need Jesus to stand
You need Jesus to bath
You need Jesus to make up
You need Jesus to comb your hair
You need Jesus to wave
Tell your neighbour - you need Jesus!
You need Jesus!
You need to know how much you need Jesus.
Viewers all over the world, I want to leave you with this message
In order to maintain your blessing, because satan is looking for every loophole
He knows when you are weak
He knows when you are not in Jesus,
He knows when you are disconnected
When you are out of prayer, you are out of Jesus!
You need to know how much you need Jesus!
You need Jesus to Smile
You need Jesus to frown
You need Jesus to sit
You need Jesus to stand
You need Jesus to dress
You need Jesus to make up!
You need Jesus to comb your hair
You need Jesus to wave
Thank you Jesus!
Hallelujah!